killping.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy Policy - Kill Ping

## Introduction

This page highlights the provisions of the privacy policy that is being implemented at Kill Ping.

We do not sell or share your data with any third-party organization(s) or platform(s), unless you give us the right to do so, and/or there is an absolute need that arises in cases where the user has intentionally misused the services and products of Kill Ping or has provided wrong information. In such cases, we are legally bound by the court of the law of the land to share information for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.

As part of our General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) efforts, Kill Ping is implementing a new data retention policy starting May 25th, 2018.

By continuing to use our service, you agree to our privacy policy.

## Data We Collect

We, at Kill Ping value privacy of our esteemed users/customers. We are the sole proprietor of the data that you provide us voluntarily via your email or direct contact form. This may include your email, payment method used, gaming session logs, user ISP, location, game and game server region.

## How We Use Your Data

We use your provided data for the sole purposes of user identification and communication. To monitor Kill Ping software performance, usability, connection stability, and service improvement, we use gaming session logs and your location.

In order to provide our users with optimum services, improve our user experience, account activation and management, troubleshooting and user tracking purposes, we share your provided data with third-party platforms, including:

**Mixpanel:** For user sessions tracking, promotions, monitoring, troubleshooting the user problems and server performance review.

**Mail Chimp:** For delivering promotions, offers, newsletter to our users.

**Hotkey:** For user account activation.

## Cookies

At Kill Ping, we use cookies to provide users with personalized content and social media ads in order to analyze our traffic to better understand user behavior, which consequently leads us to improve our products, services, and content to cater to the needs of the users. Also note that the cookies we use may change from time to time. Some cookies are placed by third party services that appear on our pages, including:

**Google Analytics:** Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.

**Live Chat:** Live Chat unique ID, controlling Window state, targeting advertising cookies.

**Crazy Egg:** Track visitor sessions, Track visitor on website.

**CloudFlare:** Used to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address and apply security settings on a per-client basis.

**Picreel:** Tracking visitors’ mouse movements, show promotions upon exit, page tracking by Picreel.

**Kill Ping:** Kill Ping Campaign Identifier, Users’ permission for allowing cookies.

If you would like to remove your cookies, please go to the banner on top of this page and click on ‘Not Agreed’. This will remove all the cookies but you it will also exit you from our website. As our website requires cookies, not agreeing will exit our website.

## Security

We are obliged to protect your data both online and offline. Wherever possible, we choose not to store your sensitive information (like payment details, Credit Cards, etc.). We only work with trusted and well reputed 3rd parties like Mixpanel, Stripe, Paypal and Bluesnap. For the bare minimum information that we have to store, we try to keep it as secure as we can.

## Data Retention

The System Administrator is responsible for determining useful data that can be retained, such as system logs, session logs, and emails. (S)he is also required to optimize the data retention schedule to gain maximum benefits of the organization (Kill Ping). Please note that we do maintain certain data, such as user information and session logs, of our unsubscribed users for the purpose of enhancing user experience and performance management of our service.

## Note on General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for EU Residents

If you are a resident of any of the European Union Member State(s), you can, at any time, exercise your ‘Right to be Forgotten’. Just drop us the request via an email at [forget@killping.com](mailto:forget@killping.com) or contact us via our Live Chat on the website and we'll erase all your data within 30 days, except your email and previous invoices since we'll need that for accounting purposes.

## Consent

Unless you opt out, you will continue to receive emails and newsletters about our products, services, and other future updates. If you would like to opt-out of our emails, please click on the unsubscribe link in our email.

## Change in Privacy Policy

We, at Kill Ping reserve the sole right to update or change any provisions of the privacy policy as and when deemed necessary, for legal compliance, or if there is a change in business practices. We are obliged to notify any alterations in the provisions of the privacy policy to you via the email that you have provided to us.

## Any Questions?

If you have any queries about the Kill Ping Privacy Policy, you can send us an email at [care@killping.com](mailto:care@killping.com).
